It's better to light one candle than curse the darkness.
Racing Extinction is a adventure, documentary film directed by Louie Psihoyos.
An unlikely team of activists and innovators hatches a
bold mission to save endangered species.
Self, played by Elon Musk.
Self, played by Jane Goodall.
Self, played by Louie Psihoyos.
Self, played by Leilani Münter.
Self, played by Charles Hambleton.
Self, played by Heather Dawn Rally.
Racing Extinction is a 2015 documentary about the ongoing anthropogenic mass extinction of species and the efforts from scientists,
activists, and journalists to document it by Oscar-winning director Louie Psihoyos, who directed the documentary The Cove (2009).
The film received one Oscar nomination, for Best Original Song, and one Emmy
nomination for Exceptional Merit in Documentary Filmmaking.
Racing Extinction premiered at the 2015 Sundance Film Festival, followed by limited theater release, with
worldwide broadcast premiere on Discovery Channel in 220 countries or territories on December 2, 2015.
Racing Extinction′s website details further information about
contemporary extinction and campaigns with which to prevent it.
The film was created by the Oceanic Preservation Society.
The film explores themes of animal species, earth,
scientist, endangered species, activist.